SONG PARK

Google Scholar Github

RESEARCH INTERESTS

I am interested in interpreting and understanding visual concepts with multiple view points (e.g., mood, emotion, style, texture) to extract better visual representations for real-world downstream tasks. To be specific, I have focused on the following research areas:

- · Representation Learning
- · Image to Image Translation
- · Style Transfer

EDUCATION

Ph.D. candidate in Integrated Technology from Yonsei University
Mar 2016 - Present Advisor: Prof. Hyunjung Shim
B.S. in Integrated Technology from Yonsei University
Mar 2013 - Feb 2016

PUBLICATIONS

- * indicates equal contribution.
 - 1. Song Park, Sanghyuk Chun, Junbum Cha, Bado Lee, Hyunjung Shim, "Multiple Heads are Better than One: Few-shot Font Generation with Multiple Localized Experts", International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2021. https://github.com/clovaai/mxfont
 - 2. Song Park*, Sanghyuk Chun*, Junbum Cha, Bado Lee, Hyunjung Shim, "Few-shot Font Generation with Localized Style Representations and Factorization", IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition Workshops (CVPRW), 2021 and AAAI Conference on Artificial Intelligence (AAAI), 2021.

https://github.com/clovaai/lffont

- 3. Joo Hyun Park*, **Song Park***, Hyunjung Shim, "Semantic-aware neural style transfer, Image and Vision Computing (**IMAVIS**), vol. 87, pp. 13-23, 2019.
- 4. Junsuk Choe*, **Song Park***, Kyungmin Kim*, Joo Hyun Park*, Dongseob Kim*, Hyunjung Shim, "Face Generation for Low-Shot Learning Using Generative Adversarial Networks", International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops (**ICCVW**), 2017.

Under Review

1. Song Park*, Sanghyuk Chun*, Junbum Cha, Bado Lee, Hyunjung Shim, "Few-shot Font Generation with Weakly Supervised Localized Representations", IEEE Transactions on Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence (TPAMI), 2021.

RESEARCH EXPERIENCES

Visiting Researcher Sep 2020 - Sep 2021

NAVER AI Lab

Mentor: Sanghyuk Chun

Research Intern Mar 2020 - Sep 2020

NAVER CLOVA

Mentor: Sanghyuk Chun, Junbum Cha, and Bado Lee

PROJECTS

Style Transfer Using Local Features

May 2021 - Present

 Developing a style transfer method which can capture and utilize local features of images without semantic labels.

Few-shot Font Generation

Mar 2020 - Apr 2021

- Generating a full font library with only a few reference glyphs.
- 2 papers are published: MX-Font (ICCV 2021) and LF-Font (AAAI 2021).
- · 2 github repositories are available: MX-Font, LF-Font
- · Working on unified few-shot font generation benchmark.

Self-supervised Deep Image Hashing

Mar 2018 - Feb 2020

· Compressing the image data into binary codes while preserving the semantic similarity.

Image Completion for Restoring Blocked Areas

Jul 2019 - Jan 2020

- · Sponsored by Electronics and Telecommunications Research Institute (ETRI).
- · Developed a module restores holes caused by blocking in Light-field and multi-viewpoint images.

Semantic Style Transfer

Dec 2018 - Feb 2019

- Resolving "semantic mismatch" problems in existing style transfer methods utilizing segmentation map.
- 1 paper is published in IMAVIS, 2019.

Reconstructing Environment Map

Nov 2017 - Feb 2018

· Predicting the surrounding environment map from a single image of the scene.

Face Generation and Recognition

Mar 2017 - Oct 2017

- · Augmenting the low-shot face dataset using GAN model to overcome limitations of low-shot learning.
- 1 paper is published in ICCVW, 2017.

Movie Poster Classification

Mar 2016 - Feb 2016

- Training a deep model which classifies a movie poster into its genres.
- · Crawled movie posters and their genres from web (IMDb).

SKILLS

Programming Languages & Frameworks (Selected)

- · Programming Language: Python
- · Machine learning tools: PyTorch, Tensorflow, OpenCV, NumPy, Scikit-learn.

SCHOLARSHIPS

Full scholarship for Graduate School

Mar 2016 - Present

Institute for Information and Communications Technology Promotion (IITP)

Full scholarship for Undergraduate School

Mar 2013 - Feb 2016

Institute for Information and Communications Technology Promotion (IITP)

TEACHING EXPERIENCES

Teaching Assistant

School of Integrated Technology, Yonsei University

• Software Project Sep 2017 - Dec 2017

• Database Sep 2016 - Dec 2016